In this case, the law of total probability will help you a lot,
この場合 全確率の公式は大いに役立ちます
so this has nothing to do with Bayes Rule.
これはベイズの法則とは関係ありません
You already heard about this important rule from Sebastian.
既にセバスチャンからこの重要な公式について聞かれたことでしょう
Do you remember? And here,
覚えていますか?ここで
we can see as a result,
状態 ｘ－１を導入し、状態は所与であるとしたことの結果を見ることができます
Then, the probability distribution of our motion model can be expressed as the
モーションモデルの確率分布は
integral of pxt given the previous states,
前の状態を与えられた pxt の積分として表現することができます
the previous observations are controls,
前回の観測値はコントロールされた値であり、
the map multiplied by the probability distribution of
マップは
the previous state itself over the whole state space xt minus one.
全体の状態空間 xt から 1 を引いた値に対して前の状態の確率分布を掛けたものです
For better understanding, assume you are only half p of xt and you introduce pxt minus 1.
判り易くするために、p xtのみで考えることにし、かつp(xt-1を導入します。
Then, you would have inside the integral pxt,
xt から 1 を引いた値と p xt から 1 を引いた値の確率分布が
given xt minus one and the probability distribution of pxt minus one itself.
積分 p xt の中に含まれる場合があります
And this is exactly the same as the example over here.
これは ここでの例とまったく同じです
But since we have conditions in our target distribution,
目標分布には条件があるため
you also have to consider them in the first and second tab.
最初と 2 番目の式で条件を考慮する必要があります
So, let us represent this situation as
それでは この状況を
a graph to visualize the dependencies between the road blocks,
道路ブロック間の依存関係を視覚化するグラフとして表しましょう
because of introducing xt minus one.
xt-1 を導入するためです
You are looking at all possible states of the previous time step
前のタイムステップで考えられるすべての状態を調べ
and then predict where the car would be in the next time step.
次のタイム ステップで車がどこにあるかを予測します
Since we also have all the other given values over here,
他の指定値もあるため
we also use this information to estimate xt.
この情報を使って xt を推定します
The same information is also use to estimate xt minus one itself.
xt から 1 を引いたものを推定するためにも同じ情報が使用されます
And of course, xt minus one is unknown.
当然、xt - 1は未知です
Now, my question is,
ここで質問です
could we simplify this relation by using meaningful assumptions?
意味のあるアサンプションを使って この関係を単純化できますか?